https://www.repligen.com/company/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy :: Repligen
×
You are using an unsupported browser.Some features of this site may not function properly. For optimal user experience, please view this site in Chrome, Firefox, Safari, or Edge.
Careers
Investors
Contact
En
Cn
Jp
Sign In
Profile
Sign Out
Toggle navigation
TechnologiesPre-packed ColumnsManufacturingOPUS 5 - 80RTechnologyGMP ManufacturingFAQRFQ ConfiguratorProcess ValidationOPUS ValiChromResin ListProcess DevelopmentOPUS RoboColumnOPUS MiniChromOPUS ValiChromOPUS CentriColumnOPUS PipetColumnResin ListATFXCell ATF Single-useXCell ATF Stainless SteelFAQServiceTFFLab-scale SystemsKrosFlo KR2iPilot-scale SystemsKrosFlo KMPiManufacturingKrosFlo KTFKrosFlo KPSSingle-use Flow PathsKF Comm 2 SoftwareServiceTFDFTFDF TechnologyTF + DF = TFDFHow it WorksPerformanceKrosFlo TFDF SystemsIntegrated SystemsApplication SupportProConnex TFDF Flow PathsStandard Flow PathsScale-upHollow Fiber FiltersSpectrum Hollow Fiber
FiltersModulesProduct Number KeyFind a Spectrum® Hollow Fiber FilterSpectrum Hollow Fiber MembranesTypesApplicationsPart Numbers and SpecificationsSingle-use Flow PathsFlat Sheet CassettesFlat Sheet MembranesProStreamHyStreamApplicationsTangenX SIUS Single-useProcess DevelopmentCommercialConfigurationsHardwareFAQTangenX SIUS GammaTangenX PRO ReusableProcess DevelopmentCommercialConfigurationsHardwareHardwareSIUSPROX-FLO 76Single-use Flow PathsSingle-use Flow PathsFlow PathsProConnex TFDF Flow PathsOrder WorkflowDialysisReady-to-use DevicesFloat-A-LyzerMicro Float-A-LyzerTube-A-LyzerAccessoriesMembranesFAQPart Numbers and SpecificationsSpectraFlo™ Dynamic Dialysis SystemsLab SystemProcess SystemMobile SystemAccessoriesMembranesDialysis Tubing and MembranesRC MembraneCE MembraneCustomized membraneClosuresAnalyticsC TechnologiesSoloVPEFlowVPEELISA KitsMabSelect SuReNGL-Impact ANative and Recombinant Protein ALONG R3 IGF-IGrowth FactorsLONG R3 IGF-ILONG EGFLigands and ResinsProtein A LigandsNGL-Impact ArSPAsrPA50Native Protein A LigandResinsCaptivAIPAOtherOperating Room DisposablesProduct developmentDisposablesLab SuppliesChromatography SuppliesApplicationsBy Therapeutic ClassProtein TherapeuticTrendsProcess FlowGene TherapyAAVLentivirusPlasmid DNAVaccinesTrendsProcess FlowMacro MoleculesProcess FlowAntibody Drug ConjugatesProcess FlowCOVID-19 SolutionsFaster Lead TimesHigh Impact SolutionsPriority SupportOperations StatusGene TherapyAAVHost Cell ExpansionMedia Exchange Pre-TransfectionViral Vector ProductionUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationViral VectorLentivirusHost Cell ExpansionMedia Exchange Pre-TransfectionViral Vector ProductionClarificationUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationViral VectorPlasmid DNAE. coli FermentationUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationFinal PlasmidPerfusion Cell CultureLong-term PerfusionAdvancesBest PracticesFed-Batch Cell CultureN-1 PerfusionHow It WorksAdvancesHigh Productivity HarvestHow It WorksAdvancesChromatographyPre-packed ColumnsMulti-column ChromatographyAdvancesDynamic DialysisResourcesSupportServiceTechnical SupportCustomer ServiceKnowledge BaseHow It WorksFiltration 101Alternating Tangential Flow (ATF)Tangential Flow Filtration (TFF)Pre-packed ChromatographyDialysisBioprocessing Process FlowsProtein TherapeuticsGene TherapyVaccinesMacro MoleculesAntibody Drug ConjugatesReferencesHollow Fiber Filter Product Number KeyPore Size ChartChemical CompatibilityWebinarsConfiguratorsRequest for Quote ConfiguratorsOPUS 5-80RTangenX Flat Sheet CassettesDesign ConfiguratorsSelection ToolsFind a KrosFlo System PartFind a Spectrum® Hollow Fiber FilterFind a Dialysis DeviceQuality DocumentsUser GuidesRegulatory Support FilesSafety Data SheetsCertificates - ExamplesQuality System Management DocumentsQuality and Animal-Free StatementsBy ProductLibraryPublicationsTechnical and Application NotesScientific PostersWhite PapersSelected Third Party ArticlesData SheetsEventsTechnical SeminarsTradeshowsSeminars | ArchiveVideosCorporateTutorialsKnowledge BaseTechnologiesApplicationsWebinarsFrequently Asked QuestionsPerfusionOPUS 5 - 80RTangenX™ SIUS™ TFF FiltersLONG R3 IGF-ILONG EGFDialysisShopeStoreRepligen E-StoreDialysisKrosFlo TFFFittings KitsHollow Fiber FiltersTangenX™ PD CassettesOPUS® MiniChrom® for AAVAnalyticsCell Culture SupplementsOperating Room DisposablesSpectra/Mesh Woven FiltersLab SuppliesCompanyAboutMissionBrandsHistoryLeadershipOfficersFunctional LeadersBoard of DirectorsScientific Advisory BoardNews RoomAnnouncementsIn the NewsNews Room ArchiveCareersWorking at RepligenCareer OpportunitiesBenefitsOperationsContactRepligenDistributorsInvestorsCorporate ProfilePress and Earnings ReleasesInvestor Presentations and EventsLeadershipCorporate GovernanceFinancial InformationInteractive Analyst CenterSEC FilingsAnnual ReportsStock InformationStock QuoteInvestment CalculatorOwnership ProfileAnalyst CoverageInvestor Contacts and AlertsFAQ
TechnologiesApplicationsResourcesShopCompanyAccountTechnologiesPre-packed ColumnsATFTFFTFDFHollow Fiber FiltersFlat Sheet CassettesSingle-use Flow PathsDialysisAnalyticsGrowth FactorsLigands and ResinsOtherApplicationsBy Therapeutic ClassCOVID-19 SolutionsGene TherapyPerfusion Cell CultureFed-Batch Cell CultureChromatographyDynamic DialysisResourcesSupportKnowledge BaseConfiguratorsQuality DocumentsLibraryEventsVideosFrequently Asked QuestionsShopeStoreCompanyAboutLeadershipNews RoomCareersOperationsContactInvestorsPre-packed ColumnsManufacturingProcess ValidationProcess DevelopmentATFXCell ATF Single-useXCell ATF Stainless SteelFAQServiceTFFLab-scale SystemsPilot-scale SystemsManufacturingSingle-use Flow PathsKF Comm 2 SoftwareServiceTFDFTFDF TechnologyKrosFlo TFDF SystemsProConnex TFDF Flow PathsHollow Fiber FiltersSpectrum Hollow Fiber
FiltersSpectrum Hollow Fiber MembranesSingle-use Flow PathsFlat Sheet CassettesFlat Sheet MembranesTangenX SIUS Single-useTangenX SIUS GammaTangenX PRO ReusableHardwareSingle-use Flow PathsSingle-use Flow PathsFlow PathsProConnex TFDF Flow PathsOrder WorkflowDialysisReady-to-use DevicesSpectraFlo™ Dynamic Dialysis SystemsDialysis Tubing and MembranesAnalyticsC TechnologiesELISA KitsGrowth FactorsLONG R3 IGF-ILONG EGFLigands and ResinsProtein A LigandsResinsOtherOperating Room DisposablesLab SuppliesChromatography SuppliesBy Therapeutic ClassProtein TherapeuticGene TherapyVaccinesMacro MoleculesAntibody Drug ConjugatesCOVID-19 SolutionsFaster Lead TimesHigh Impact SolutionsPriority SupportOperations StatusGene TherapyAAVLentivirusPlasmid DNAPerfusion Cell CultureLong-term PerfusionAdvancesBest PracticesFed-Batch Cell CultureN-1 PerfusionHigh Productivity HarvestChromatographyPre-packed ColumnsMulti-column ChromatographyAdvancesSupportServiceTechnical SupportCustomer ServiceKnowledge BaseHow It WorksBioprocessing Process FlowsReferencesWebinarsConfiguratorsRequest for Quote ConfiguratorsDesign ConfiguratorsSelection ToolsQuality DocumentsUser GuidesRegulatory Support FilesSafety Data SheetsCertificates - ExamplesQuality System Management DocumentsQuality and Animal-Free StatementsBy ProductLibraryPublicationsTechnical and Application NotesScientific PostersWhite PapersSelected Third Party ArticlesData SheetsEventsTechnical SeminarsTradeshowsSeminars | ArchiveVideosCorporateTutorialsKnowledge BaseTechnologiesApplicationsWebinarsFrequently Asked QuestionsPerfusionOPUS 5 - 80RTangenX™ SIUS™ TFF FiltersLONG R3 IGF-ILONG EGFDialysiseStoreRepligen E-StoreDialysisKrosFlo TFFFittings KitsHollow Fiber FiltersTangenX™ PD CassettesOPUS® MiniChrom® for AAVAnalyticsCell Culture SupplementsOperating Room DisposablesSpectra/Mesh Woven FiltersLab SuppliesAboutMissionBrandsHistoryLeadershipOfficersFunctional LeadersBoard of DirectorsScientific Advisory BoardNews RoomAnnouncementsIn the NewsNews Room ArchiveCareersWorking at RepligenCareer OpportunitiesBenefitsContactRepligenDistributorsInvestorsCorporate ProfilePress and Earnings ReleasesInvestor Presentations and EventsLeadershipCorporate GovernanceFinancial InformationStock InformationAnalyst CoverageInvestor Contacts and AlertsFAQManufacturingOPUS 5 - 80RProcess ValidationOPUS ValiChromResin ListProcess DevelopmentOPUS RoboColumnOPUS MiniChromOPUS ValiChromOPUS CentriColumnOPUS PipetColumnResin ListLab-scale SystemsKrosFlo KR2iPilot-scale SystemsKrosFlo KMPiManufacturingKrosFlo KTFKrosFlo KPSTFDF TechnologyTF + DF = TFDFHow it WorksPerformanceKrosFlo TFDF SystemsIntegrated SystemsApplication SupportProConnex TFDF Flow PathsStandard Flow PathsScale-upSpectrum Hollow Fiber
FiltersModulesProduct Number KeyFind a Spectrum® Hollow Fiber FilterSpectrum Hollow Fiber MembranesTypesApplicationsPart Numbers and SpecificationsFlat Sheet MembranesProStreamHyStreamApplicationsTangenX SIUS Single-useProcess DevelopmentCommercialConfigurationsHardwareFAQTangenX PRO ReusableProcess DevelopmentCommercialConfigurationsHardwareHardwareSIUSPROX-FLO 76Ready-to-use DevicesFloat-A-LyzerMicro Float-A-LyzerTube-A-LyzerAccessoriesMembranesFAQPart Numbers and SpecificationsSpectraFlo™ Dynamic Dialysis SystemsLab SystemProcess SystemMobile SystemAccessoriesMembranesDialysis Tubing and MembranesRC MembraneCE MembraneCustomized membraneClosuresC TechnologiesSoloVPEFlowVPEELISA KitsMabSelect SuReNGL-Impact ANative and Recombinant Protein ALONG R3 IGF-IProtein A LigandsNGL-Impact ArSPAsrPA50Native Protein A LigandResinsCaptivAIPAOperating Room DisposablesProduct developmentDisposablesProtein TherapeuticTrendsProcess FlowGene TherapyAAVLentivirusPlasmid DNAVaccinesTrendsProcess FlowMacro MoleculesProcess FlowAntibody Drug ConjugatesProcess FlowAAVHost Cell ExpansionMedia Exchange Pre-TransfectionViral Vector ProductionUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationViral VectorLentivirusHost Cell ExpansionMedia Exchange Pre-TransfectionViral Vector ProductionClarificationUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationViral VectorPlasmid DNAE. coli FermentationUltrafiltration and DiafiltrationPurificationConcentration and FormulationFinal PlasmidN-1 PerfusionHow It WorksAdvancesHigh Productivity HarvestHow It WorksAdvancesHow It WorksFiltration 101Alternating Tangential Flow (ATF)Tangential Flow Filtration (TFF)Pre-packed ChromatographyDialysisBioprocessing Process FlowsProtein TherapeuticsGene TherapyVaccinesMacro MoleculesAntibody Drug ConjugatesReferencesHollow Fiber Filter Product Number KeyPore Size ChartChemical CompatibilityRequest for Quote ConfiguratorsOPUS 5-80RTangenX Flat Sheet CassettesSelection ToolsFind a KrosFlo System PartFind a Spectrum® Hollow Fiber FilterFind a Dialysis DeviceFinancial InformationInteractive Analyst CenterSEC FilingsAnnual ReportsStock InformationStock QuoteInvestment CalculatorOwnership Profile
Repligen responds to COVID-19: Operations Status
Privacy Policy
Repligen is committed to protecting your Personal Information. This Global Privacy Policy applies to the public’s use of repligen.com (the “Website”) and outlines how Repligen deals with consumer Personal Information provided to us or is otherwise collected via the Website or through other sources separate from the Website. If you disagree with the terms of this Global Privacy Policy, do not use the Website.
If you are a resident of California or Nevada in the United States, you may have additional rights regarding your personal data. More information may be found in our California and Nevada Privacy Policy.
Personal Information
Repligen may collect information that you choose to provide through the Website, and may gather information automatically through your use of this Website, including, without limitation, IP addresses, site navigation, etc. (See the Section below on “Cookies”) and from other sources separate of the Website (for example, order forms, customer service, and/or the like) (“Personal Information”). When you visit certain areas of the Website, request or download, information, shop, submit a request for quotation (RFQ) or purchase products, register for events, participate in surveys, subscribe to company newsletters, submit a resume, or participate in programs administered through this Website, we may ask you to register or provide Personal Information and preferences. This may include, without limitation, your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, payment information during checkout for online purchases, and other information depending on the context of your visit to this Website.
If you submit any personal data relating to other people to us, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Global Privacy Policy.
Use of Personal Information
The Personal Information you provide may be used to fulfill your request, process your order, manage your account, provide products and/or services, provide customer service, marketing, communicate with you, or otherwise operate our business. For example, Repligen may use this information to alert you to company news, new products, company events, and other company and product information. Your Personal Information may also be used for profiling for the same purposes described above; you may object to profiling via automated-decision making by contacting via the contact information provided below. We may also store, use and analyze anonymous data provided by users or derived from Website usage for statistical purposes and other business purposes, for example, to monitor and improve Repligen’s business.
Unless otherwise specified, the legal basis for the handling of your personal data results from the fact that such handling is required to make available the functionalities of the Website requested by you.
Protection of Personal Information
When visitors to this Website provide Personal Information, we strive to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the sensitive information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Repligen stores information in a controlled, secure environment. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure, and we cannot guarantee your personal data will be secure from theft, loss, or unauthorized access or use. Repligen makes no representation as to the reasonableness, efficacy, or appropriateness of the measures we use to safeguard such data. Users are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of their own user account information, including passwords. If you believe that your user account information is no longer secure, please notify us immediately.
Your data will may also be processed in countries outside the European Union (“EU”) or the European Economic Area (“EEA”), which may have a lower data protection level than European countries. In such cases, we will ensure that a sufficient level of protection is provided for your data, for example, through specific agreements with our contractual partners or we will ask for your explicit consent to such processing.
Third Party Access
Repligen does not sell information to third parties, but reserves the right, at the sole discretion of Repligen, to share any and all information with select partners or related parties including but not limited to, distribution partners, consultants, resume management services, online payment services, promotional agencies, etc. We will only provide the information they reasonably need to deliver the service or product, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by law, when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with a regulatory requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, government request, or legal process served on us, or to protect the safety, rights, or property of our customers, the public, Repligen or others.
Links
This Website may contain links to other third-party websites that are not under the control of Repligen. Repligen is not responsible for the privacy policy of any other third-party website linked to this Website. Repligen provides links to other websites as a convenience to users, and access to any other third-party websites is at your own risk. Repligen encourages you to read the privacy policies of these other third-party websites.
Cookies and other Tools
We may use cookies and other tools on this Website to collect information. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on the hard drive of your computer and is used to identify your computer on return visits to this Website. Cookies may be used to customize your visits and to monitor use of this Website. If you block or decline to accept a cookie, you may still use the Website. However, some parts of this Website may not permit access and some functionality may be lost or modified.
Spam Policy
At Repligen, we have a zero-tolerance Spam policy. Our internal systems will filter out any communication that contains the same characteristics found commonly in Spam messages. In some instances, legitimate messages may be filtered out by our security systems. Please contact us at webmaster@repligen.com if you believe a legitimate message was filtered out in error.
Additionally, we strive to deliver relevant, applicable messages and content to our opted-in users through frequent email communications. If you receive a message from us that you consider to be Spam, please contact us at webmaster@repligen.com in order for us to investigate the occurrence.
Business Transitions
If Repligen undergoes a business transition such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ Personal Information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified through a notice posted on this Website at the time of a change of ownership or control of their Personal Information.
Access and Data Privacy Rights
If you request access to your Personal Information collected on this Website, we will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of such information as allowed by law, and provide you access to that information. You may withdraw your consent to the future use of your Personal Information at any time on request.
The following rights are generally available to you according to applicable data privacy laws, including the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”):
You have the right to request copies of your personal data.
You have the right to request correction of any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that Repligen complete the information you believe is incomplete.
You have the right to request that Repligen erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
You have the right to request that Repligen restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
You have the right to request that Repligen transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.
If you believe we are using, disclosing, or otherwise processing your Personal Information in a way that is not in accordance with applicable laws, you can lodge a complaint with a data protection authority in your country.
We will handle any request to exercise your rights in accordance with applicable law. Please note that depending on the circumstances, some of the above rights may not be applicable.
Modifications
Repligen reserves the right to modify this Global Privacy Policy at any time, and any changes made will be posted directly to this Website. Any changes will be effective when posted to this Website. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Global Privacy Policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please contact us by emailing legal@repligen.com or calling 800.622.2259.
© Copyright 2020 Repligen Corporation. All rights reserved.
Contact
Privacy Policy
Legal
Careers
